Register of the German subject collection, 1873-2012
Hoover Institution Archives
- FEDERAL REPUBLIC OF GERMANY, 1949-1990 October 2
  - Elections (Box 58)
    - 1976. Pamphlets, leaflets, flyers, newspaper issues, pins and buttons, flags, and a song book relating to the general elections of, October 3, 1976 (Box 59)
      - Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands (SPD)
        - General
        - General (Box 61)
        - Deutsche Jungdemokraten (DJD)
        - Jungsozialisten der Sozialdemokratischen Partei Deutschlands (JUSO)
    - Leaflets, pamphlets, newspaper issues and posters relating to the general elections of 1980
      - Christlich-Demokratische Union Deutschlands (CDU)
      - Freie Demokratische Partei (FDP)
      - Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands (SPD)
    - 1983. Pamphlets, leaflets, flyers, newspaper issues and ephemeral material relating to the general elections of, March 9, 1983
      - General
      - Christlich-Demokratische Union Deutschlands (CDU)
        - General
      - Christlich-Demokratische Union Deutschlands (CDU)
        - General (Box 62)
        - Junge Union Deutschlands
      - Christlich-Soziale Union (CSU)
      - Deutsche Kommunistische Partei (DKP)
      - Deutsche Volksunion
      - Foderation demokratischer Arbeitervereine aus der Turkei (Box 63)
      - Freie Demokratische Partei (FDP)
      - Grune Partei
      - National-Demokratische Partei Deutschlands (NPD) (Box 64)
      - Marxistisch-Leninistische Partei Deutschlands (MLPD)
      - Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands (SPD)
        - General
        - Deutsche Jungdemokraten (DJD) (Box 65)
        - Liberale Demokraten (LD)
        - Liberaler Hochschulverband (LHV)
    - General elections. Brochures and stickers, 1984
      - Christlich-Demokratische Union Deutschlands(CDU)
      - Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands (SPD)
    - 1987. Newspapers issues, reports, flyers, newsletters, pamphlets, brochures and ephemeral material relating to the general election of, January 25, 1987
      - General
      - Christlich-Demokratische Union Deutschlands (CDU)
      - Christlich-Soziale Union (CSU)
      - Deutsche Kommunistische Partei (DKP)
      - Freie Demokratische Partei (FDP)
      - Grune Partei (Box 66)
      - Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands (SPD)
      - Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands (SPD) (Box 67)
    - 1989 (Box 68)
      - Communal elections, June 18
      - Auslanderbeiratswahl in Ludwigshafen, December 12.
    - 1990 May 13
      - Christlich-Demokratische Union Deutschlands (CDU)
      - Freie Demokratische Partei (FDP)
      - Gewerkschaft Offentliche Dienste (OTV)
      - Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands (SPD)
    - European elections, 1994 June 12
  - Movements and organizations, 1983-1990
    - General, 1989-1990
    - Amnesty International fur Gewerkschafter, 1984
    - August Bebel Gesellschaft, 1984
    - Deutscher Freidenker-Verband
    - Ehrenbund Rudel
    - El Salvador Komitee, n.d.
    - Gemeinschaft Deutscher Osten, 1990
    - Humanistische Union, 1990
    - Jugendwerk der Arbeiterwohlfahrt (JW), 1987-1990
    - Komitee der Kampfer fur den Frieden in Westdeutschland
    - Marxistische Gruppe (MG), 1983
    - Mut zur Einheit, 1983
    - National Offensive, 1990
    - Nationalistische Front (NF), 1986-1989
    - Nordische Zukunft, 1989 (Box 69)
    - Peace movement, 1982-1983 (Box 115)
    - Schlesische Jugend, 1984 (Box 69)
    - Volksbewegung fur Generalamnestie, n.d.
  - Newspapers and periodicals, 1987-1990
    - General
      - Alptraum Auto Abschaffen, 1990
      - Antifaschistische Maizeitung, 1990
      - Antifaschistische Nachrichten, 1990
      - Antifaschistische Zeitung, 1990
      - Arbeitsmarkt, 1990
      - Berlin Informiert, 1990
      - Berliner Luft-Zeitung, 1989-1990
      - Berliner Morgenpost, 1990
      - Berliner Tageblatt, n.d.
      - Berliner Zeitung (B.Z.), 1990
      - Bild Zeitung, 1990
      - Blatt, Das, 1990
      - Blatt Extra, 1990
      - Blick Nach Rechts, 1990
      - Blickpunkt, n.d.
      - Blind, 1990
      - Bolschewistische Tendenz, 1990
      - Criticon, 1990
      - DDR Heute, 1990
      - Deutscher Standpunkt, 1990 (Box 70)
      - Dritte Welt, 1990
      - Frankfurter Allgemeine Zeitung, 1989
      - Freie Presse Korrespondenz, 1990
      - Grenzenlos, 1990
      - Klassenkampf, 1990
      - Kommunale Rundschau fur die DDR, 1990
      - Kreuzberger Stachel, 1989-1990
      - Madelbrief, Der, 1990
      - Markt Wirtschaft, 1990
      - Nation und Europa, 1989-1990
      - Neue Zeitung Berlin West, 1989
      - Neues Berlin, 1989
      - Neues Journal, n.d.
      - Nie Wieder Deutschland, 1990
      - Ostfriesen Zeitung, 1990
      - Ostwirtschaft Intern, 1990
      - Parlament, Das, 1990
      - Platt Form, 1990
      - Politische Zeitung, 1989
      - Projekt Wochenzeitung, 1990
      - Report, 1990
      - Scala, 1990
      - Scheinschlag, 1990
      - Stars and Stripes, 1990
      - Stern, 1989
      - Stern, 1990 (Box 71)
      - Tacheles, 1990
      - Tagespiegel, Der, 1989-1990
      - Transmitter, 1989
      - Unabhangige Nachrichten, 1987
      - Welt, Die, n.d.
      - Weltbild, 1989
      - Wochenblatt, 1990
    - Political parties and organizations
      - Christlich-Demokratische Union Deutschlands (CDU)
        - Berliner Rundschau, 1990
        - CDU Extra, n.d.
      - Freie Demokratische Partei, Forum Liberal, 1990
      - Grune Partei, Schoneberger Stichel, 1990
      - International Communist League, Le Bolchevik, 1990
      - Nationaldemokratische Partei Deutschlands (NPD), Deutsche Stimme, 1990
      - Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands
        - Gustrower Anzeiger, 1990
        - Neue Charlottenburger Zeitung, 1990
        - Voran, 1989-1990
      - Trotkzistische Liga Deutschlands, Spartakist, 1989-1990
  - Political parties, 1957-1990 (Box 72)
    - Christlich-Demokratische Union Deutschlands (CDU), 1978-1990
    - Christlich-Soziale Union (CSU), 1986-1990 (Box 73)
    - Deutsche Alternative (DA), 1989-1990
    - Deutsche Kommunistische Partei (DKP), 1968-1969
    - Deutsche Soziale Union (DSU), 1990
    - Deutsche Volksunion (DVU), 1989
    - Deutsche Zentrumspartei, 1989
    - Europaische Volkspartei, 1989
    - Freie Demokratische Partei (FDP), 1957-1990
    - Freie Demokratische Partei (FDP) (Box 74)
    - Freiheitliche Deutsche Arbeiterpartei (FAP), 1983-1989
    - Grune Partei, 1986-1990
    - Grune Partei (Box 75)
    - Kommunistische Partei Deutschlands (KPD), 1990
    - Marxistisch-Leninistische Partei Deutschlands, 1990
    - Nationaldemokratische Partei Deutschlands (NPD), 1971-1990
    - Nationalsozialistische Deutsche Arbeiterpartei Auslands - und Aufbauorganisation (NSDAP/AO), 1989-1990
    - Okologisch-Demokratische Partei, 1982
    - Republikaner, 1988-1990
    - Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands (SPD)
    - Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands (Box 76)
  - Politics and government, See also GERMAN DEMOCRATIC REPUBLIC-Politics and Government and UNIFIED GERMANY-Politics and Government, 1968-1990.
    - General. Publications relating to the Federal Republic of Germany's political and economic policies, Arranged by publisher, 1969-1990.
      - General, 1977-1990
      - Government
        - Bundesminister fur Arbeit und Sozialordnung, 1990
        - Bundesministerium fur innerdeutsche Beziehungen, 1989-1990
        - Bundesministerium fur innerdeutsche Beziehungen (Box 77)
        - Bundesministerium fur wirtschaftliche Zusammenarbeit
        - Bundesministers des Innern, 1990
        - Bundesministers der Justiz, 1990
        - Bundesrat, 1989-1990
        - Bundestag, 1989-1990
        - Presse- und Informationsamt der Bundesregierung, 1969-1990
    - Federal Office of Statistics. Includes material on the GDR's economic and social development, 1990
    - Kohl, Helmut. Includes printed biography and text of speeches, 1989-1990 (Box 78)
    - Kreuzberg district, West Berlin, 1984
    - Unification. See also GERMAN DEMOCRATIC REPUBLIC-Politics and Government-Unification and UNIFIED GERMANY-Politics and Government-Unification
      - General, 1990
      - Currency unification. See also FEDERAL REPUBLIC OF GERMANY-Subject file-Economic policy-Deutsche Bank
        - General. Includes printed text of the Currency, Economic and Social Union Treaty, 1990
        - Aktuelle Beitrage zur Wirtschafts- und Finanzpolitik, 1990
        - Bulletin, 1990
        - Federal Law Gazette, 1990
        - Record of the 11th Parliament of the Bundestag, 1990
        - Record of the 11th Parliament of the Bundestag (Box 79)
        - Stenographic report of the Bundesrat, Sessions 613-615, 1990
        - Stenographic report of the Bundestag, Session 212 and 217, 1990
      - Political unification
        - General. Newspapers, periodicals, printed text of the Unification Treaty, 1958-1990
        - General (Box 80)
        - Commission of the European Community, 1990 (Box 81)
        - Federal Law Gazette, 1990
        - Opposition to, 1990
        - Record of the 11th Parliament of the Bundestag, 1990
        - Stenographic report of the Bundesrat, Session 618, 1990
        - Stenographic report of the Bundestag, Sessions 222 and 226, 1990
        - Stenographic report of the Committee for German Unification of the Bundestag, Sessions 10-11, 13, 15, 17-20, 1990 (Box 82)
        - United Nations, 1990
      - Treaty of Friendship, Partnership and Cooperation between the Federal Republic of Germany and the Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, 1990 September
  - Student protest movement. Periodicals, pamphlets, leaflets, proclamations and posters issued by leftist student groups relating to West German and international political issues, including the West German emergency laws, the publisher Axel Springer, the visit of the Shah of Iran to Berlin, the invasion of Czechoslovakia and the Vietnam War, 1967 1968 1966-1983
    - General
      - General
      - Africa (Box 83)
      - Biafra
      - Czechoslovakia
      - Emergency laws, 1968
      - Greece
      - Iran
      - Israel
      - Springer, Axel
      - Turkey
      - University reform
      - Vietnam
    - Organizations
      - General
      - Aktionsgemeinschaft Demokratische Universitat (ADU)
        - General
        - Unireport
      - Aktion Osterreich Europa
      - Ausserparlamentarische Opposition (APO). See also Universities, Berlin, Freie Universitat; Munich
        - General
        - Arbeiter-Basis-Gruppen (Box 84)
        - Ausserparlamentarische Opposition Press
      - Allgemeiner Studenten Ausschuss (AStA). See also Universities, Freiburg; Gvttingen; Hamburg; Hanover; Heidelberg; Munich; Stuttgart; Tubingen; and Subject file, Biafra; Emergency laws; Greece
        - General
        - Basisgruppen-AStA-Fraktion, Aufwind
        - Berlin. See also Universities, Berlin, Freie Universitat)
        - Bonn. See also Universities, Bonn
        - Munchen
          - General
          - Munchner Studentenzeitung
      - Bonner Studentenschaft
      - Bremer Gruppe, Arbeiterpolitik
      - Demokratische Alternative, Hamburg
      - Deutsche Kommunistische Partei (DKP), Munchen. See also Universities, Freiburg and subject file, Vietnam
      - Europaisch Foderalistischer Studentenverband (EFS). See also Universities, Berlin, Freie Universitat; and subject file, Greece
      - Evangelische Studentengemeinde Gottingen
      - Freiheit der Wissenschaft, Bonn
      - Gewerkschaftlicher Arbeitskreis der Studenten (GAST)
        - General
        - GAST-Flugblatt
      - Gruppe Germanistik, Berlin. See also Universities, Berlin, Freie Universitat
      - Humanistische Studenten Union (HSU). See also Universities, Berlin, Freie Universitat; Tubingen
      - Junge Nationaldemokraten (JN) der Nationaldemokratische Partei Deutschlands (NPD)
      - Junge Union Deutschlands der Christlich-Demokratische Union (CDU)
      - Jungsozialisten der Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands (SPD), Munchen (JUSO). See also Universities; Freiburg
        - General
        - JUSO-Information
      - Katholische Hochschulgemeinde Munchen, Univox
      - Katholische Studentengemeinschaften (KSG)
      - Liberaler Studentenbund Deutschlands (LSD). See also Universities, Berlin, Freie Universitat; Bonn; and Subject file, Biafra; Greece (Box 85)
        - General
        - Liberale Studentenzeitung
      - Marxistisch-Leninistische Studentengruppe (MLS). See also Universities, Berlin, Freie Universitat
      - Marxistischer Studentenbund (MSB) Spartakus. See also Universities, Freiburg; Munich
      - Munchner Studenten Union (MSU)
        - General
        - P.S.: Presse der Studenten
      - Partei der Universalisten
      - Republikanische Hilfe
      - Republikanischer Studentenbund Deutschlands (RSD)
      - Ring Christlich-Demokratischer Studenten (RCDS). See also Universities, Berlin, Freie Universitat; Freiburg
        - General
        - Aktuell
      - Ring Freiheitlicher Studenten (RFS)
      - Sozialistischer Deutscher Studentenbund (SDS). See also Universities, Berlin, Freie Universitat; Frankfurt am Main; Heidelberg; Tubingen; and Subject file, Vietnam
        - General
        - Rote Presse Korrespondenz
        - SDS-Wandzeitung
      - Sozialistischer Hochschulbund (SHB). See also Universities, Bonn; Freiburg
      - Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands (SPD). See also Universities, Berlin, Freie Universitat; Freiburg; and Subject file; Notstandgetsetz
      - Unabhangige Arbeiter-Partei (UAP)
      - Unabhangige Skat-Spieler-Vertretung (USSV)
      - Verband Deutscher Studentenschaft (VDS). See also Universities, Berlin, Freie Universitat; Marburg
      - Vereinigte Deutsche Studentenschaften (VDS)
    - Periodicals and newspapers (Box 86)
      - Agit 883: Kampfblatt der kommunistischen Rebellion
      - Aktuell
        - Berlin
        - Frankfurt am Main
      - Andere Deutschland, Das
      - Anrisse
      - Anschlag
      - Bild
      - Bundschuh, Der
      - Dynamis
      - Hochschul Magazin
      - Information
      - Konturen
      - Linke Linse
      - Log Sondernummer
      - Neue 883, Frankfurt am Main
      - Neue Bildpost
      - Phil-Fak Zeitung. See also Berlin, Freie Universitat
      - Phrasen Maher
      - Politikon
      - Politikstudent, Der
      - Sozialistische Korrespondenz
      - Student
      - Studenten Anzeiger (Box 87)
      - Suddeutsche Zeitung
      - Venceremos
      - Berkeley, University of California. German radio transcript and rebuttal relating to student unrest on the Berkeley campus, Typescript, 1969 May.
      - Berlin, Freie Universitat
        - Undated
        - 1966-1967
        - 1967
        - 1968
        - 1968 (Box 88)
        - 1969
        - 1969 (Box 89)
        - 1970
        - 1971
        - 1973
        - Freie Universitat Information (FU), 1969-1970 (Box 90)
        - Freie Universitat Pressedienst (FU), 1969
        - Freie Universitat Spiegel (FU), 1967-1968
        - Otto-Suhr-Institut and Freie Universitat Berlin, 1967-1969
      - Bochum, Ruhr-Universitat
      - Bonn
        - 1967-1969
        - 1970-1972
        - 1973-1974 (Box 91)
      - Frankfurt am Main, 1968-1973
      - Freiburg im Breisgau
        - 1967-1971
        - 1972-1973
        - 1973 (Box 92)
        - 1974
      - Friedrich-Meinecke-Anstalt, 1969
      - Georg-August-Universitat
      - Gottingen, 1968
      - Hamburg (Box 93)
        - 1967-1968
        - 1969-1972
      - Hanover, 1967-1974
      - Heidelberg, 1970-1972
      - Johann-Wolfgang-Goethe-Universitat Frankfurt, 1972
      - Marburg, 1965-1970
      - Munich, 1968-1972
      - Nurnberg, 1969
      - Stuttgart, 1967-1970
      - Tubingen, 1968-1972
      - Tubingen (Box 94)
  - Subject file, 1960-1990
    - General, 1966-1990
    - Astronautics, 1966
    - Ecology, 1989-1990
    - Economic policies, See also FEDERAL REPUBLIC OF GERMANY-Politics and Government-Unification, 1983-1990.
      - General, 1986-1990
      - Deutsche Bank. Includes material on the German Democratic Republic, the Soviet Union, Eastern Europe and German currency unification, 1989-1990
      - Deutsche Bank (Box 95)
      - Labor and labor unions
        - General, n.d.
        - Deutscher Gewerkschaftsbund (DGB)
        - Disputes-35 hour week, 1983-1984
        - Gewerkschaft Offentliche Dienste, Transport und Verkehr (OTV), 1983
        - Industriegewerkschaft Druck und Papier
      - United States, 1987
    - Foreign aid, 1960
    - Foreign relations
      - Allied occupation forces, 1952
      - German Democratic Republic. Includes printed copy of the Basic Treaty with the Federal Republic of Germany, 1973-1988
      - Poland, 1966
      - Soviet Union, 1989-1990
      - United States, Includes material on the Gulf War, 1983-1990.
    - Human rights
      - General, 1990
      - Warsaw Pact nations, 1989
    - Immigration
      - General, 1971-1990
      - Auslander (foreigners)
        - General, 1980-1989
        - Guest workers, 1984-1989
      - Aussiedler (citizens of eastern and western European nations who are of German ancestry), 1988-1990 (Box 96)
      - Aussiedler and Ubersiedler, 1989-1990
      - Ubersiedler (citizens of the former German Democratic Republic), 1989-1990
    - Jews, 1990
    - Media, 1971
    - Military
      - Bundeswehr
      - North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO)
        - General, 1986-1988
        - Opposition to deployment of nuclear and conventional weapons on German territory, 1983-1984
    - National socialism. Printed book order lists relating to the role of national socialism during and after World War II (Box 97)
    - Personal experiencs and correspondence, 1990
    - Racism and anti-racism, 1990
    - Sud-West Staat. Posters, 1952
    - Terrorism. Includes wanted posters for a group of terrorists led by Willy Peter Stoll, Friedrike Krabbe; Helmut Pohl and others, reports relating to the hijacking of a Lufthansa airplane; and a CDU compilation of references to terrorism, 1977
    - Weizsacker, Richard Freiherr von, 1989
    - Women
      - General, 1984-1990
      - Arbeitsgemeinschaft Sozialdemokratischer Frauen in der Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands (ASF in der SPD), 1984
      - Deutscher Akademikerinnen Bund E.V., 1984-1990
      - Deutscher Frauenring E.V., 1988
      - Deutsche Kommunistische Partei (DKP), 1984
      - Frauenbundnis '90
      - Frauen Museum, Bonn, 1984
      - Katholische Arbeitnehmerbewegung, 1989
      - Katholischer Deutscher Frauen Bund
      - Ludwigshafen am Rhein, 1990
  - Youth movements. Radio broadcast typescripts, published articles relating to the youth movement, the "Wandervogel-Bewegung" and various youth movements after World War II, 1908-1973 (Box 98)
    - Adler, H.C., "Wanderer zwischen den Welten: Die deutsche Jugendbewegung, " broadcast of the Westdeutschen Radio, Koln, 1913-1933, 1963 May 4
    - Aff, Johannes, "Wanderwege," Typescript, 1955 May.
    - Kayser, Friedrich, "Wandervogel: Idee und Wirklichkeit," broadcast of Sender Freies Berlin, Berlin, 1962 June 23
    - Linz, Gertraud, "Die Erben der 'Blauen Blume,'" broadcast of Hessischen Rundfunk, Frankfurt am Main, 1967 August 5
    - Merlin, Rafael W., "Wandervogel und Blau-Weiss," broadcast of Hessischen Rundfunk, Frankfurt am Main, 1968 July 30
    - Mitgau, Hermann, "Der Feldwandervogel,", 1951
    - Nipperdey, Thomas, "Zur Lage an der Freien Universitat," broadcast of Sender Freies Berlin, Berlin, 1969 March 25
    - Pross, Henry, "Das Gift der blauen Blume," broadcast of Sender Freies Berlin, Berlin, 1961 November 3
    - Report of the "1. Padagogischen Woche,", 1949 November 20-27
    - Rosenberg, Alwin, "Die Artamanenbewegung," Typescript
    - Rothweiler, Charlotte, "Jugend im Vorfeld der Politik," broadcast of Norddeutschen Rundfunk, Frankfurt am Main, 1967 August 5
    - Schadendorf, Hanna, "Das Alte Schloss," Typescript, 1973.
    - Schirrmann, Richard, "Edmund Neuendorff zum 80. Lebenjahr,", 1955
    - Schmidt-Zettel, Herbert, "Funfzig Jahre Fahrtenleben mit der Jugend!"
    - Schmidt-Zettel, Herbert, "Vom Leben der Wandervogel," documentary report
    - Schoeps, Hans-Joachim, "Die unbewaltigte Vergangenheit,", 1960
    - Sontheimer, Kurt, "Das Reich der Unpolitischen," broadcast of Sudwestfunk, Baden-Baden, 1961 October 18
    - Thumes, Karl, "Ursprunge und Wurzeln, Anfange und Gestaltungskrafte bundischer Korporationen in Osterreich,", 1966 November 13
- UNIFIED GERMANY, 1990 October 3- (Boxes 99-126)
  Election party material, newspaper issues, magazines, printed matter, typescripts, catalogs, newsletters, booklets, bulletins, pamphlets, arranged alphabetically by subject
  - Elections
    - General (Box 99)
    - Landstag election which took place only in the former 14 districts of the GDR and re-created the five Bundeslander of Brandenburg, Mecklenburg-Vorpommern, Sachsen, Sachsen-Anhalt, and Thuringen, 1990 October 14.
      - General
        - General
        - Brandenburg
        - Mecklenburg-Vorpommern
        - Results
        - Sachsen
        - Sachsen-Anhalt
        - Thuringen
      - Bundnis '90
        - General
        - Brandenburg
        - Sachsen
      - Christlich-Demokratische Union Deutschlands (CDU) (Box 99, 116)
        - General
        - Brandenburg (Box 99)
        - Mecklenburg-Vorpommern
        - Sachsen
        - Sachsen-Anhalt
        - Thuringen
      - Christlich-Soziale Union (CSU)
      - Christliche Liga
        - Sachsen
        - Thuringen
      - Demokratie Jetzt
      - Deutsche Kommunistische Partei (DKP)
      - Deutsche Soziale Union (DSU)
        - General
        - Mecklenburg-Vorpommern
        - Sachsen
        - Sachsen-Anhalt
        - Thuringen
        - Domowina
        - Freie Deutsche Jugend (FDJ)
      - Freie Demokratische Partei (FDP)
        - General
        - Brandenburg
        - Mecklenburg-Vorpommern
        - Sachsen
        - Sachsen-Anhalt
        - Thuringen
      - Grune Partei (Box 100)
        - General
        - Brandenburg
        - Sachsen
        - Sachsen-Anhalt
        - Thuringen
      - Nationaldemokratische Partei Deutschlands - Sachsen-Anhalt
      - Nelken (Box 116)
        - General
        - Brandenburg (Box 100)
      - Neues Forum
        - Mecklenburg-Vorpommern
        - Sachsen
        - Sachsen-Anhalt
        - Thuringen
      - Partei des Demokratischen Sozialismus (PDS)
        - General
        - Brandenburg
        - Mecklenburg-Vorpommern
        - Sachsen
        - Sachsen-Anhalt
        - Thuringen
      - Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands (SPD) (Box 100, 116)
        - General
        - Brandenburg (Box 100)
          - General
          - Stolpe, Manfred
        - Mecklenburg-Vorpommern
        - Sachsen
        - Sachsen-Anhalt
        - Thuringen
      - Senioren-Schutz-Bund der Deutschen Demokratischen Republik (SSB der DDR) - Brandenburg
      - Unabhangige Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands (USDP) - Brandenburg
      - Unabhangiger Frauenverband (UFV) - Thuringen
      - Vereinigte Linke (Box 116)
    - (All-German Election), 1990 December 2 (Box 101, 116)
      - General
      - Antiparlamentarian movement (Box 116)
      - Berlin (Box 101)
      - Bundnis '90
        - General
        - Grune Partei (Box 102)
        - Neues Forum
        - Neues Forum (Box 113)
      - Christlich-Demokratische Union Deutschlands (CDU) (Box 102, 116)
      - Christlich-Soziale Union (CSU) (Box 116)
      - Deutsche Soziale Union (DSU)
      - Freie Demokratische Partei (FDP) (Box 102, 117)
      - Grauen, Die (Box 102)
      - Nationaldemokratische Partei Deutschlands (NPD)
      - Partei des Demokratischen Sozialismus (Box 102-103, 117)
      - Republikaner, Die (Box 103)
      - Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands (SPD) (Box 103, 117)
      - Vereinigung der Arbeitskreise fur Arbeitnehmerpolitik und Demokratie (VAA) (Box 103)
    - (Communal elections), 1993 December 5 (Box 118)